### Contact

aryandas1402@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ aryandas-1402 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Engineering

Research

Management

### Languages

Bengali (Professional Working) Hindi (Professional Working)

English (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Python Essentials

Certificate for Python Basics for Data Science

edX Verified Certificate for AWS: Getting Started with Cloud Security

**Cloud Computing Core** 

edX Verified Certificate for Introduction to Cloud Computing

# Aryan Das

Social Media Coordinator at Mechomotive Kolkata

## Summary

Computer Science Engineering Student | Coder | Illustrator Passionate about building something that would solve a problem in our day to day life.

Learning more about Data Science and Machine Learning Algorithms that would help me to do research work in this field.

Coding Languages I am expert at:

- > C
- > C++
- > Java

Languages I will learn in the upcoming days:

- > R
- > Python
- > JavaScript
- > SQL
- > MatLab

Would love to connect with Learning Enthusiasts in the field of Data Science and work with them.

## Experience

Pie Rooms Social Media Marketing Intern February 2021 - March 2021 (2 months)

Mechomotive Social Media Coordinator February 2021 - March 2021 (2 months)

## Education

University of Engineering & Management (UEM)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2020 - 2024)